[Annie] Previously on Sterling Point…
[Marjorie] So sorry
about your grandfather's passing.
Connor and Annie Jacobson.
Gordon has made you
the beneficiaries of his trust.
It includes a parcel of land in Canada.
Gordon wrote us letters our entire lives.
Dad hid 'em in a safe.
[Connor] We're not even
biologically related.
The last letter that Gordon wrote.
he said. "Find her."
-Find who?
-Exactly! Something's going on.
We have to figure out what's happening.
"Annie. find her." [sighs]
-Annie? Hi. yeah. Ellis. your pilot.
-Hi.
[Ellis] Welcome to Sterling Point.
Old owner said he'd never rent it.
-[Annie] You knew him?
-He owned this island.
[softly] Hey. Mom.
Is it weird
that girl's renting Gord's cottage?
What girl is renting his cottage?
Wait. Annie? Annie Jacobson?
[Annie] Rory.
Wait. so why are you here?
My mom spent time here.
Actually. is your mom here?
-Hi.
-Oh. my. Annie Jacobson.
Your mother. she was so upset.
That's what finally led her to filing.
For divorce from your dad.
[gasps] Jesus!
-Who are you?
What are you doing
in my grandfather's cottage?
["H.E.R." playing]
[Ramona] Hello?
[gasps] Jesus!
Who are you?
What the fuck are you doing
in my grandfather's cottage?
-Hello?
-Sorry.
Hi. Um. I-I…
I thought that this was my cottage.
-You thought this was your cottage?
-I mean. my Airbnb.
-Um. I'm so sorry. What is your name?
-I'm not telling you!
What's your name?
Also. this isn't an Airbnb.
How long have you been here?
I just got here today.
Then why is there hundreds of bottles
of stuff in the bathroom?
Those are my creams.
-Uh. sorry. My name's Annie.
-Yeah. Cool.
Nice to meet you. Annie. Pack up your shit
and leave now. I won't press charges.
Jesus Christ.
[objects clattering]
[softly] Oh. my God.
[breath trembling]
I noticed that you look a lot like
the woman in the pictures on the wall.
That's a very creepy thing to say
right now. I'm not gonna lie.
Totally.
I'm sorry. I meant that as a compliment.
Like. you guys are…
both so pretty.
Are you related?
[Ramona] Kinda.
She's my mom.
There aren't any Airbnbs on the island.
-so you should start at Port Carling.
-Wait! Sorry.
Is there no way I can chill here tonight.
and we can discuss this in the morning?
That's a "Fuck no." Uh-uh.
Can we please talk about this
for a second? This is a little bit crazy.
Are you kicking me out
-in the middle of the night?
-Yeah.
-I can provide a background check.
-Don't care.
[Annie] Oh! What the fuck? I thought
Canadians were supposed to be friendly.
-[Ramona] Not true.
-[slams door]
Okay.
[Annie sobbing]
-[softly] Jesus Christ.
-[sobbing continues]
-Dude. you do not have to cry.
-I…
I can cry if I want. I actually have
a lot to cry about right now. so…
What's your full name. so I can google
your background check?
It's. um…
Annie Jacobson.
-You gonna tell me yours?
-No.
Okay.
[Ramona] You can sleep on the couch
for one night.
I'll feel bad if a bear eats you.
But you have to be gone in the morning.
Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
I can't tell you
how much I appreciate this.
Um. is your mom coming too.
by any chance?
Is your mom coming? What…
Or are you just airbnb-ing an island
in Canada alone?
-What kinda question is that?
-Well. my mom is dead. so…
Sorry.
No. sorry. It's fine. It was. like. a…
long time ago.
My name is Ramona.
My mom is dead too.
[exhales softly]
[exhales]
[beeps]
[softly] Connor. call me. period.
There's a girl here
who looks just like Mom. exclamation mark.
I'm freaking the fuck out.
Did Mom have a secret bio daughter?
Question mark.
question mark. question mark.
[text message chiming]
And so much drama re Mom and Dad. period.
and. quote. Grandpa. end quote.
-[phone beeps]
-[text message chiming]
Fuck. Why are all these going green?
Exclamation point. exclamation point.
[phone beeps]
I didn't even download Love Island.
It's so fucking dark.
[creaks]
-["Deck the Halls" chiming on clock]
-[gasps]
[exhales anxiously]
[grunts] Fuck!
You said you'd be gone by morning.
It's morning.
Was that really necessary?
-You better be gone when I'm back.
-[door slams]
Awesome.
["Back on You" playing]
Come on.
I just need one fucking bar.
Okay.
Okay. This is fine.
All good.
-[engine revving in distance]
-Whoa. [chuckles softly]
Oh. fuck!
Shit. Oh. shit.
Shit. Shit. shit. shit. shit. Oh!
Oh. shit.
Fuck. fuck. fuck.
Okay. Okay.
Does this not do anything?
Shit. shit. Fuck!
[exclaims] Oh. fuck.
Oh. fuck! Fuck.
Oh. shit. [grunts]
No! No. no. no.
No. no. no!
["Mr. Eclectic" playing]
Fuck!
Fuck me. Fuck!
Yes. yes.
No!
Oh. Don't!
Don't run me over!
[Rory] Hey!
-Hey!
-What's up?
Fancy seeing you here.
Okay. I know what this looks like.
It's a classic "man rescuing a woman
from a near-death experience."
Yeah. No. it's not…
Not exactly what this is.
-It's fine. I'll just swim home.
-No. No. Uh…
I got this.
-Amazing.
-Okay?
-Life's good.
-Okay.
Everything's going to plan.
Right here. Go long.
Yo. you need help?
Don't break your back. You're old.
-I am not that old. for God's sake.
-[chuckles]
-I didn't know you were comin' up.
-Did you think I'd just dip forever?
Well. I would hope not. but I had no idea.
So it's really…
[Ramona] Yeah. I'm here.
And…
not going anywhere. so get used to it.
-[Joe] Hey. Ramona. wait. Listen.
-Yeah.
All right. if you need anything. will you…
I won't. But thank you for the concern.
[Sully] All right. all right. all right.
Okay. GF and DF for Maple.
-My God. Yum. Thank you.
-[Sully] No salsa verde for Ellis.
-[Ellis] Thank you!
-[Ramona] Extra cheese on mine.
by any chance?
No? [exhales]
Ouch! Sully. what did I ever do to you?
Guys. it's a joke.
What the fuck happened to you
while I was gone?
Ramona. what?
Oh. my God!
-Hi!
-Hey!
Like. can I touch you? Are you real?
You are real. Hello. Oh. my God!
-I can't even… When did you get here?
-Yeah.
-Last night.
-And you didn't tell us? Why?
'Cause I got back last night!
-We're good.
-Oh. my God. Are you staying? Oi.
I don't know.
Depends on if I still have a job.
I mean. you've criminally overused
your vacation days. but whatever.
-So. that's a yes.
-[all chuckle]
Um. I'm actually so sorry.
I didn't get you one.
And I know yours gets extra cheese.
Everyone knows that. So I'm sorry.
Hey. you gorgeous little freak.
Stop apologizing for everything.
It's fine. You're perfect.
You don't have to apologize
ever again. okay?
-Yeah. Not even a problem. Sorry.
-Yeah. You're fine.
-What? Whoa! Thanks.
-Welcome back.
Thanks.
-What are these?
-Oh. they're shirts.
-That's right. Marina--
-Oh. my God!
-Marina…
-Marina Crew.
["Off the Rails" playing]
Whoo!
Jump!
[chuckles]
-[gasps]
-[all laughing]
[Sully] No!
-Catch it next time. please.
-I'll try my best. Thank you.
How do I look?
-All right.
-Okay.
-Got it?
-Yep.
You know. I called you.
Like. a lot.
Sorry. It's actually
a lot harder than you'd think.
taking care of a dying old man.
Ramona. I…
I was really worried about you.
And I missed you. man.
I'm glad you're back.
And I'm really sorry you had to
go through all of that by yourself.
Yeah. I'm fine now.
Thanks.
So. like. who's taking care of you?
I mean.
me. [chuckles]
-You know how it is.
-Mmm.
Gordon set you up with everything
that you need and everything?
Yeah. I mean.
I have the cottage and the island and…
Everything. I'm good.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
You look so good.
-In your mom's clothes?
-Okay. Yeah. that's weird.
-But it's perfect for the party.
-Party?
No party. Gathering.
-Okay.
-Super low-key. Super casual vibes.
-I'll let you get settled.
-Oh. yeah. I…
Do you guys have service here?
I need to call Connor about something.
-Yeah. you can use the Starlink.
-Oh!
-Thank you so much.
-Yes. I will give you some privacy.
-Thank you.
-All right.
-Bye.
-[door closes]
Okay.
Do I…
Do I wanna add a farm-fresh egg on top?
[tutting]
Yeah. why not?
[cell phone buzzing]
Oh. my God.
What do you want? You're so annoying.
I lost my entire order
from 4 Charles to pick this up.
-Wait. you're home?
-Yeah.
-Oh. she dumped you?
-Shut up.
Oh. how is Canada?
Dad still thinks you're in Thailand.
So you're welcome for that.
He does? Good. Thank you.
Because I have some very intense news.
Oh! So do I. actually.
-I think we have a secret sister.
-Oliver put a Pride flag in his Insta bio.
I think we should address mine first.
-Connor!
-Okay. when you say "sister."
do you mean. like. biological family?
No. Our mom. Our adoptive mom.
I hate that word. but whatever.
I think she had a secret
biological daughter.
because there is a girl here
-who is an exact clone of her.
-Okay.
But Dad's a sterile king.
They couldn't have kids.
That's why they adopted us.
I know. But clearly.
something isn't adding up.
'cause this girl is. like. our age-ish.
And she said that
it's her grandfather's cottage too.
who apparently owned
the entire island. Oh! Oh!
And everybody loved Gordon. by the way.
So. not sure what Dad's thing
with him being an asshole is.
Wait. we own an island?
Is it super nice or no?
Because I was just next
to Mike White at Barry's Bootcamp.
Should season nine
of White Lotus be set there?
-Oh. I heard Haley Joel Osment is coming--
-Connor. focus!
The other big thing is that
Mom filed for divorce from Dad.
-Strange.
-I feel like it has to do with this girl.
So I guess our sister?
Okay. Hold on a second.
Let's not throw the S word around
without knowing the full story.
I mean. does Dad know about her?
Connor. I don't know.
And please do not tell him anything
'cause he will fly here and drag me home
before I figure out what's going on.
I'm actually really impressed
you're doing this.
Thanks. Really wanna get to the truth.
No. I'm impressed that you're lying.
especially to Dad. This is huge for you.
Okay. Yeah. Thanks.
Sorry about Capucine.
Thanks.
[sighs] And I'm sorry
that your boyfriend came out publicly
before he came out to you.
Also that it looks like he's having
an incredible summer.
And also that I'm pretty sure
he's being spit-roast
by his new boyfriend
and a very hot. rich. older Thai man.
-And also--
-Okay. bye.
Dick.
Let's see.
Fuck.
It's broken.
Dad. I… My phone stopped working.
I need a new one.
[Oona] Stop splashing.
-Watch the hair.
-Ramona. come in.
-No. I'm good.
-[Oona] Come in. baby. Please.
-[Ellis] Get in.
-It's nice. though?
-It'd be so much nicer if you were in it.
-Come on.
It'll be so good.
-Boo!
-[Sully] You can borrow my tube.
-[Oona] Get in.
-[Sully] A Marco Polo moment?
-[Oona] Yeah. yeah. yeah.
-[Sully] Marco.
-Bitch. you're supposed to say "Polo."
-Polo.
[Sully] Thank you. I was like…
-Marco.
-[Oona laughs]
Marco.
[Oona] Polo.
-[Sully] Marco.
-Hey.
Hey.
Sorry I didn't. like. call or anything.
No. No. no. no.
It's honestly okay.
Did you have. like…
anyone. at least?
-What do you mean?
-Like. to be with you.
Friends from school?
Girlfriend?
No. Isn't that so depressing?
Are we both just gonna be
girlfriend-less forever?
What about Airbnb Annie?
She's giving single and bi.
Wait. what?
-How the fuck do you guys know Annie?
-We hung out all Canada Day.
-She's pretty cool.
-And night.
Didn't you rent the cottage
to her. though?
No. I did not rent the cottage to her.
I don't know who the fuck this girl is.
Wait. wait. wait.
I kinda assumed you guys
were. like. friends or something.
-'cause she knew Gordon owned it.
-No.
Friends? No.
She told me her dead mom used to
summer here. and that's why she came.
Okay. What the fuck?
Is this bitch a robber? Identity theft?
No. Honestly. I didn't get
criminal energy from her.
It was just more. like.
really sweet and kind and. like.
beautiful.
I think you'd really like her.
She's so cute. She's lovely.
Maybe she's. like.
a teenage real estate agent
who's trying to trick you into
selling the island to the Four Seasons.
-Girl. what?
-[Ellis] Teenage real estate agent? Right.
Or she could be 40 and just have
an incredible skin-care routine.
Wait. Actually. she does have
an insane skin-care routine.
I saw. like. 75 bottles of shit
in the bathroom.
-Seventy-five?
-75? That's insane. Okay. A bit overkill.
But it's not that weird that she's here.
Think about it. There are hundreds
of rentals on these islands.
She probably just got lost and confused.
Also. Ramona. who's gonna convince you
to sell the island? No one.
Don't stress about it.
-Are you saying that 'cause she's hot?
-She is not hot.
Yes. she is. She is hot.
Have you seen her side profile?
Yeah. I need to make sure she's gone
and didn't steal anything.
What would she steal?
[Ramona] Okay. stop defending her
just 'cause you like her. It's annoying.
-[Ellis] Guess we're leaving.
-Okay. Ramona. I don't like her.
[Ramona] Right.
-[Oona] Okay. come on.
-[Ramona] Come on.
-[Oona] Come on. Maple.
-[engine starts]
Marco?
Friends?
Hello? Hello?
-Jesus.
-[Ramona] Sorry.
[scoffs]
What is she looking for?
I don't know. It's Ramona.
Everything still here?
Yeah. I think so.
Good.
And she's gone?
Yeah. I guess she's gone.
I think I was meant to be at work.
like. 45 minutes ago.
How have you not been fired yet?
Truly one of the greatest mysteries
of our time.
Can you give me a ride. please?
You coming?
[Ramona] Yeah.
Fries on the way back?
Mmm.
What the…
["Bad Dreams" playing]
[chattering indistinctly]
-[chuckles] Oh. you guys.
-It was lovely to meet you.
So nice to meet you guys.
See you in a bit.
-Catch you around.
-Good to see you.
-Okay.
-Do you want a drink?
Uh. yes. I'm actually gonna say hi
to your mom real quick.
-Gin and water?
-Uh. yeah. Yes. thanks.
What's that?
-I'm so--
-Sorry. Hi.
-Hi!
-Hi. Oh. my God!
Thank you so much
for letting me stay. Seriously.
Never leave. Honestly.
I'm making you stay all summer.
Wait.
Where did you get this dress? Turn around.
-[gasps] Look at your butt.
-Oh. thank you. It's…
actually yours.
What's mine?
-The dress. I'm so sorry.
-[chuckles]
Not anymore.
Listen. let's get you a drink.
because you're way too sober.
-Yes. I am.
-You are like "Mmm!"
I know. Actually. really quick. Sorry. Um…
Could I ask you about
what you said yesterday?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-About my mom filing?
-Yeah. yeah. of course.
-Yeah. I was just curious. Um…
How did you know that?
Well. everybody in the city knew
because your dad came back from Muskoka
with two children and no wife.
Connor and I were in Muskoka with my mom?
Yeah. she brought you here for the summer.
But then she never… never went home.
I'm sorry. honey. Yeah.
Oh. my God. my lawyer is puking
in the shrimp cocktail. Hold. please.
Isaiah. okay. let's get you outside.
Perfect.
This good. Mom?
-Why do I have to be here chopping shit?
-Oona.
This is a front-of-house face.
You get me in trouble every event
by making out with all the married women.
My mom said we can't have that anymore.
I never initiate.
-Okay. occasionally I initiate.
-Girl.
I'm just gonna…
[Rory] Yeah. Yeah.
-That's true. [laughing]
-I thought she was gone.
-Hey.
-[breathing heavily]
-You okay?
-Yeah.
What?
I just feel…
I just feel like I can hardly breathe.
Um. okay.
You're good. You're good. Uh…
[gasping]
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
-I literally forgot I was holding this.
-And you're done.
Can we. like. talk about it. please?
You feel like you can get some air in now?
Yeah. a little.
Cold water on the bottom of the feet.
it helps. um. regulate the vagus nerve.
I used to get horrible panic attacks too.
Helped me a lot. If it doesn't help you--
-No. This is really nice.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. it's helping a lot.
-Okay.
[Rory exhales]
I just feel like everything I knew
about myself was wrong.
Okay.
That's a scary feeling. to feel so. um…
untethered.
Yeah. actually.
that's a really good word for it.
Just. like. yeah. kind of untethered.
Why are you feeling like that?
Yeah. um…
Yeah. Being here is making me realize
how little I think about my mom.
Well.
you're thinking about her now.
[chuckles sadly] Yeah. Yeah.
But you love salt-and-vinegar chips.
It's the same thing.
-What're you saying?
-It's not.
-Hey.
-I thought you were working.
No. I got fired
because I almost stabbed someone.
-Huh?
-What?
-Oh. but Annie was there at the party.
-What party?
-Just some party at Rory's house.
Why is she with him?
I don't know. But I was forced to leave
before I could talk to her.
No. I need to figure out
what the fuck is going on with her.
Hey. maybe. like. play it chill. though.
Would you be chill
if someone broke into your house
and stole a photo of your dead mom?
That is actually kinda weird.
["Sinner" playing]
Hey. Uh…
-You mind. like. slowing down a bit?
-Shut up.
-Go faster.
-Just a little bit.
A little quicker.
-Ramona. I'm actually feeling a bit sick.
-Oh. hey!
[yelling] Hey! I am so onto your ass!
Oh. I fucking see you.
-Yep. Yep. Hey.
-Ramona. slow down!
[Ramona] Do not move an inch!
-Ramona.
-Oh. hey. so you found your Airbnb.
Yeah. this place looks totally
like my place. I get it.
-Yeah.
-I can explain this.
-Oh. you can explain?
-Yes.
I'd love for you to explain why you lied.
-why you know my grandfather's name…
-Ramona--
…why you broke into my cottage
and stole a photo of my dead mother.
why the fuck you're here?
I can honestly explain--
-Why'd you steal a photo of my dead mom?
-'Cause she's my mother too!
What did you just say?
She's my mother too. [sighs]
And I don't know anything that's going on.
but I think that we might be sisters.
Oh. shit.
-Get in the boat.
-Why?
-Just get in.
-[Annie] Okay.
That girl is not gonna kill her. right?
No.
I'm almost positive that's a no.
-You guys will check on Annie?
-Yeah. we got it.
Is there a small part of you
that isn't sure Ramona won't kill her?
-Yeah.
-Same. Okay. let's go.
[Annie] I'm sorry. would you mind
slowing down a little?
Okay. okay.
We're gonna hit that.
Fuck!
Tell me everything you know.
-Okay. Um…
-Now.
Okay. Goldie was… is my mom.
Uh. my adoptive mom.
And she and my dad adopted me
and my twin brother. Connor.
when we were newborns.
Uh. and then she died of cancer
when we were two. and…
um. I never knew anything
about this place or you.
Then a lawyer called when Gordon died.
and I found a letter that said.
"Find her." which I'm now assuming is you.
And my dad was acting really weird.
which made me so suspicious
that I decided…
I decided that I would just come here
and see it for myself.
And then I saw you.
and you looked so much like her
that I knew
that you were her daughter too.
Did you know about me?
No.
Great. So. like. everyone's been
lying to us our whole life.
That's actually. like. so fucked up.
Why would they wanna keep us apart?
We're sisters.
You said you were adopted?
Yeah.
So we're not related.
You're not my sister.
You go back to New York now.
Forever would be ideal.
Hey.
-Hey.
-I was looking for you.
-Hey. [chuckles]
-Um…
-How bad was it?
I would describe it as. like…
soul-crushing.
[sighs] Fuck.
-She hates me.
-What?
-[chuckles sadly] Yeah.
-No. she doesn't. okay? Ramona is…
She's complicated.
She's had a pretty rough year…
or rough couple of years. actually.
Gordon was her only family.
Now she's alone. you know?
Sorry. I didn't mean. like…
I didn't mean you're not her family.
-Sorry. I meant--
-No.
-I didn't take it that way at all.
-Okay. Sorry.
No. you're good. you're good.
Yeah. [chuckles]
I mean. we're not really. so…
Where's her dad?
Just never really been in the picture.
Apparently. he was this random tourist
who Goldie had a fling with.
Like. while she was married to my dad?
That just. like…
I'm sorry. That just does not sound like
my mom at all.
Like. to have an affair with a random guy
and then never tell…
Like. not tell your husband that you have
another daughter? That's. like…
I guess I don't really
know my mom at all. though. so…
[chuckles nervously]
what the fuck do I know?
I think there's probably
a lot more to the story. right?
Like. should I…
[hesitates] I don't really know
what to do.
Do you think I should just leave?
Do you feel like you got
the answers you wanted?
I feel like I've barely
scratched the surface.
Maybe that's your answer.
[Ramona] Don't come in.
I found it in his briefcase after he died.
and I just haven't gotten myself
to open it.
And now I feel like I have to.
'cause she said she got a letter too…
So. no. Sorry.
You don't have to open it
just 'cause she's opened a letter.
Yeah. but what if it says something
about her or…
I mean. it might.
[sighs] Why can't I open it?
Because it's the last unopened letter
that you'll ever get from your grandpa.
Of course you don't wanna read it.
It's sad.
It's a lot.
You read it.
What?
Don't read it out loud.
Just read it in your head and then…
I don't know. I can gauge from the look
on your face if I can read it.
Wait. are you sure?
Yes. It's okay. I swear. It's okay.
I won't freak out on you.
What?
Do you want me to tell you?
No. I just… Is it bad?
'Cause it seems like it's bad.
-Is it--
-You should read it.
No. Mmm-mmm.
Annie is not lying.
My mom had one daughter.
and that was me. She--
That girl did not even know her.
There's no way.
I know. I know.
But. Ramona. you didn't know her either.
Right. Yeah.
["Sequence 02" playing]
I think I got it from here.
Sure? I don't mind. like…
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah.
Are you coming or not?
[dramatic music playing]